REHAN MAHMOOD

Milton, ON L9T | 647 938 4111 | rehanmahmood38@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Hardworking Freelance Writer offering 3+ years of experience. Practiced in narrative writing and journalism. Writes quickly with focus on quality and adherence to client requirements. Skilled in social media strategies and search engine optimization. Successful background of producing high-volume, top-notch unique and insightful work.

Skills

- Creative writing
- Research
- Proofreading
- Adobe suite expertise
- Python expertise
- Dedicated and Driven
- Customer assistance
- Point of Sale Knowledge

- Editing
- Copywriting
- Networking skills
- Microsoft Office expertise
- Team-minded
- Cash register operations
- Stocking and Replenishing

Work History

High School Math and English Tutor

09/2019 to Current

Self Employed - Milton, ON

- Spearheaded group tutoring sessions to help students struggling in similar areas.
- Developed students confidence though attentive instruction in English and Mathematics, applying positive reinforcement strategies.
- Collaborated with students to complete homework assignments, identify lagging skills and correct weaknesses.
- Supported teacher instruction by discussing concepts and creating custom practice questions.
- Created special handouts, study guides and assessments to evaluate and boost student knowledge.

Sales Associate 11/2017 to 08/2019

Adidas – Halton Hills

- Organized racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers and promote specific merchandise.
- Completed scheduled audits with efficient and accurate approach.

- Supported promotional plans by updating signage with price changes.
- Trained and developed new sales team associates in products, selling techniques and company procedures.
- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Tracked stock using company inventory management software.
- Applied security and loss prevention training toward recognizing risks and reducing store theft.
- Analyzed and properly processed product returns, assisting customers with finding alternative merchandise to meet needs.
- Maintained records related to sales, returns and inventory availability.

Golf Course Associate

04/2017 to 09/2017

Glencairen Golf Course - Milton, ON

- Delivered information to visitors, including details of interest about facility, rules, policies and promotional events.
- Oversaw refreshments counter, selling food items to customers and maintaining sufficient stock of products and supplies to meet expected needs.
- Resolved guest issues by identifying source of complaint and formulating corrective action with supervisor.
- Operated rides and attractions according to written guidelines to reduce injuries.
- Issued tickets to customers and collected payment and fees for desired services.

Education

Bachelor of Science: IT Network Security

Expected in 04/2023

Sheridan College Institute of Technology And Advanced Learning - Oakville, ON

Preformed exceptionally well throughout English class